Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1, Section 1: Boxes 1-22
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1, Section 1: Boxes 1-22
- Box: 17, Folder: 2 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: The Profession of Management, Publication (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Box: 17, Folder: 3 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: A Do-it Yourself Manual on Practical Politics, Publication (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Box: 17, Folder: 4 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Press Release re. Future of Railways, Publication (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: The Railroad CrisisTime for Action, Publication (Box 17, Folder 4)
    By Clair M. Roddewig. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Press Release re. Railroad Safety, Publication (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: The Course of Railway Labor Legislation, Publication (Box 17, Folder 4)
    By Daniel P. Loomis. Item is in English.
- Box: 17, Folder: 5 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Apprentice School Lessons for Sheet-Metal Worker Apprentices, Publication (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Apprentice School Lessons for Painter Apprentices, Publication (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Apprentice School Lessons for Special and Graduate Apprentices, Publication (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Apprentice School Lessons for Machinist Apprentices, Publication (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Apprentice School Lessons for Blacksmith Apprentices, Publication (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Apprentice School Lessons for Carman Apprentices, Publication (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: Drawing; Car Department Book 1-4, Publication (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Box: 17, Folder: 6 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Training Apprentices, Publication (Box 17, Folder 6)
    By F.W. Thomas. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Railroad, Publication (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Box: 17, Folder: 7 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Agreement between Various Railroad Companies and their Employees, Publication (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Box: 17, Folder: 8 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Training Plan-ARCO Indoctrination for Houston Oil Company People, Publication (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Box: 17, Folder: 9 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Plan Your Career, Publication (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Box: 17, Folder: 10 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: A Case History in Salary and Wage Administration, Publication (Box 17, Folder 10)
    By Samuel L.H. Burk. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Atlantic Magazine; Vol. 17 No 5, Publication (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: Take a Look at Tomorrow, Publication (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Item 4: Group Medical Expense Plan for Management Employees, Publication (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Item 5: Statement Governing Employee Discount Gratuity, Publication (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Item 6: Accidental Death and Benefit Policy, Publication (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Item 7: Leaves of Absence without Pay, Publication (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Item 8: Regulations governing absence with pay, Publication (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Item 9: Provisions governing extended military service, Publication (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Item 10: Regulation governing payment of meal allowances to group A employees, Publication (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Item 11: Gratuity Provisions Governing Absence due to sickness in immediate family - Group B Employees, Publication (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Item 12: Highlights of the Thrift Plan, Publication (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Item 13: Your Group Life Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Item 14: Maintenance Manual for Job Analysis and Evaluation, Publication (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Box: 17, Folder: 11 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Corporation Information, Publication (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Box: 17, Folder: 12 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Agreement between Atlas and United Steelworkers of America at Senter Plant, Publication (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Item 2: Agreement between Atlas and United Mine Workers of America - Reynolds Plant, Publication (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Item 3: Agreement between Atlas and United Mine Workers of America - Reynolds Plant, Publication (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Item 4: Checklist of Material Needed on Company Industrial Relations Activities, Publication (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Item 5: Facts about your atlas disability plan, Publication (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Item 6: Group Life Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Item 7: Agreement between Atlas and Local No. 9-571 Oil Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union, AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Item 8: Pension Plan, Publication (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Item 9: Blue Cross-Blue Shield Plan for Employees, Publication (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Item 10: Agreement between Atlas and International Chemical Workers Union Local Number 130 AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Item 11: Agreement between Atlas and United Plant Guard Workers of America Local 107, Publication (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Item 12: Facts about your atlas employee benefit plans, Publication (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Item 13: Agreement between Atlas and International Chemical Workers Union Local Number 130 AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Item 14: General Rules and Regulations, Publication (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Item 15: Trainee Bulletin for Technical Personnel, Publication (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Item 16: Agreement between Atlas and United Mine Workers of America Local 12886, Publication (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Item 17: Agreement between Atlas and United Mine Workers of America Local 12886, Publication (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Item 18: Agreement between Atlas and United Mine Workers of America Local 12886, Publication (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Item 19: Suggestion Plan, Publication (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Item 20: Agreement between Atlas and United Workers of America Local 13101, Publication (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Item 21: Agreement between Atlas and United Plant Guard Workers of America Local 107, Publication (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Item 22: Agreement between Atlas and Local No. 9-571 Oil Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union, AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Item 23: The Atlas Story, Publication (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Item 24: Agreement between Atlas and United Mine Workers of America Local 13101, Publication (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Item 25: Agreement between Atlas and United Steelworkers of America Local 4316, Publication (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Item 26: Continuity of Service Rules, Publication (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Item 27: Group Life Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Item 28: Disability Wage Plan for Payroll Employees, Publication (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Item 29: Your Career Opportunities, Publication (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Item 30: Deferred Compensation Plan, Publication (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Item 31: Life Insurance Plan for Hourly Employees, Publication (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Item 32: The Atlas Family; Vol. 15 No. 3, Publication (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Item 33: The Atlas Family; Vol. 12 No. 6, Publication (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Item 34: Vacation Plan for Salary Roll Employees, Publication (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Item 35: News Release re. Safety, Publication (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Item 36: Bulletin No. 34 and Chart of IR dept., Publication (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Item 37: Your Career Opportunities, Publication (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Item 38: Annual Report, Publication (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Item 39: Career Opportunities, Publication (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Item 40: Career Opportunities, Publication (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Item 41: Agreement between Atlas and Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union and Its Local No. 4-367, Publication (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Item 42: Workmen's Compensation Benefit Plan, Publication (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Item 43: Contract Revisions, Publication (Box 17, Folder 12)
    By G.P. Teel. Item is in English.
  - Item 44: Disability Wage Plan for Payroll Employees, Publication (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Item 45: Comprehensive Insurance, Publication (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Item 46: Summary of Amendments to the Pension Plan, Publication (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Item 47: Pension Plan, Publication (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Box: 17, Folder: 13 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Corporate Moving Policy Manual, Publication (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Item 2: Corporate Moving Policy Manual, Publication (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Box: 17, Folder: 14 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: You and Your Company, Publication (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Item 2: Employee Disability Benefits, Publication (Box 17, Folder 14)
- Box: 17, Folder: 15 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Why Does the Auto Union Cause so much Trouble in the Automotive Industry?, Publication (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Item 2: Sit-Down - 2 Copies, Publication (Box 17, Folder 15)
    By William J. Cronin. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: AMA'S Million-Dollar Auto Record, Publication (Box 17, Folder 15)
    By Bob Finlay. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: AMA Puts Patent in Its Place, Publication (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Item 5: Auto Statistical Center, Publication (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Item 6: AMA Battles Truck Barriers, Publication (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Item 7: AMA - The Home of Auto Facts, Publication (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Item 8: AMA's Branch Nerve Centers, Publication (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Item 9: Watchdog of Vast Transport Network, Publication (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Item 10: AMA's Workers of the Impression, Publication (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Item 11: The Case of the Missing Steel, Publication (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Item 12: Keeping Tabs on 15,000 Legislative Bills, Publication (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Item 13: From Economics to Oomph!, Publication (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Item 14: Special Series on AMA, Publication (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Item 15: AMA Constitution, Publication (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Item 16: Reconversion Brings American Industry to the Crossroads, Publication (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Item 17: New Frontiers of the Auto Industry, Publication (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Item 18: Automobile Jobs, Publication (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Item 19: Constitution and By-Laws, Publication (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Item 20: A Chronicle of the Automotive Industry, Publication (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Item 21: Technological Change, Publication (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Item 22: What do your employees known about your company?, Publication (Box 17, Folder 15)
- Box: 18, Folder: 1 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Wages and Hour Statistical Data, Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Letter to President Truman, Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
    By Frank Rising. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: What Fringe Payments Cost, Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Memos to Management, Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Political Action, Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Memos to Management, Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Memos to Management, Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: Memos to Management, Publication (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Box: 18, Folder: 2 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Leaf Spring Group (Wage) Report, Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Leaf Spring Group (Wage) Report, Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Leaf Spring Group (Wage) Report, Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Leaf Spring Group (Wage) Report, Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Leaf Spring Group (Wage) Report, Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Leaf Spring Group (Wage) Report, Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: Leaf Spring Group (Wage) Report, Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: Leaf Spring Group (Wage) Report, Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: Leaf Spring Group (Wage) Report, Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Item 10: Leaf Spring Group (Wage) Report, Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Item 11: Leaf Spring Group (Wage) Report, Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Item 12: Leaf Spring Group (Wage) Report, Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Item 13: Leaf Spring Group (Wage) Report, Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Item 14: Leaf Spring Group (Wage) Report, Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Item 15: Leaf Spring Group (Wage) Report, Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Item 16: Leaf Spring Group (Wage) Report, Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Item 17: Leaf Spring Group (Wage) Report, Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Item 18: Leaf Spring Group (Wage) Report, Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Item 19: Leaf Spring Group (Wage) Report, Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Item 20: Leaf Spring Group (Wage) Report, Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Item 21: Leaf Spring Group (Wage) Report, Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Item 22: Leaf Spring Group (Wage) Report, Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Item 23: Leaf Spring Group (Wage) Report, Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Item 24: Leaf Spring Group (Wage) Report, Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Item 25: Leaf Spring Group (Wage) Report, Publication (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Box: 18, Folder: 3 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Toledo Wage Rate Report, Publication (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Box: 18, Folder: 4 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: AAPM Bulletin 276-953, Publication (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Box: 18, Folder: 5 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Chicago Wage Rate Report, Publication (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Box: 18, Folder: 6 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Lined Bearing Group Wage Report, Publication (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Lined Bearing Group Wage Report, Publication (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Lined Bearing Group Wage Report, Publication (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: Lined Bearing Group Wage Report, Publication (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: Lined Bearing Group Wage Report, Publication (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: Lined Bearing Group Wage Report, Publication (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: Lined Bearing Group Wage Report, Publication (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Item 8: Lined Bearing Group Wage Report, Publication (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Item 9: Lined Bearing Group Wage Report, Publication (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Item 10: Lined Bearing Group Wage Report, Publication (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Item 11: Lined Bearing Group Wage Report, Publication (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Item 12: Lined Bearing Group Wage Report, Publication (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Item 13: Lined Bearing Group Wage Report, Publication (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Item 14: Lined Bearing Group Wage Report, Publication (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Item 15: Lined Bearing Group Wage Report, Publication (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Item 16: Lined Bearing Group Wage Report, Publication (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Item 17: Lined Bearing Group Wage Report, Publication (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Item 18: Lined Bearing Group Wage Report, Publication (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Item 19: Lined Bearing Group Wage Report, Publication (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Item 20: Lined Bearing Group Wage Report, Publication (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Item 21: Lined Bearing Group Wage Report, Publication (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Item 22: Lined Bearing Group Wage Report, Publication (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Item 23: Lined Bearing Group Wage Report, Publication (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Item 24: Lined Bearing Group Wage Report, Publication (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Item 25: Lined Bearing Group Wage Report, Publication (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Item 26: Lined Bearing Group Wage Report, Publication (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Item 27: Lined Bearing Group Wage Report, Publication (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Item 28: Lined Bearing Group Wage Report, Publication (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Item 29: Lined Bearing Group Wage Report, Publication (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Item 30: Lined Bearing Group Wage Report, Publication (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Item 31: Lined Bearing Group Wage Report, Publication (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Item 32: Lined Bearing Group Wage Report, Publication (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Item 33: Lined Bearing Group Wage Report, Publication (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Item 34: Lined Bearing Group Wage Report, Publication (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Item 35: Lined Bearing Group Wage Report, Publication (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Item 36: Lined Bearing Group Wage Report, Publication (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Item 37: Lined Bearing Group Wage Report, Publication (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Item 38: Lined Bearing Group Wage Report, Publication (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Item 39: Lined Bearing Group Wage Report, Publication (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Item 40: Lined Bearing Group Wage Report, Publication (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Item 41: Lined Bearing Group Wage Report, Publication (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Item 42: Lined Bearing Group Wage Report, Publication (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Item 43: Lined Bearing Group Wage Report, Publication (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Item 44: Lined Bearing Group Wage Report, Publication (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Item 45: Lined Bearing Group Wage Report, Publication (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Box: 18, Folder: 7 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Michigan Wage Rate Report, Publication (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Box: 18, Folder: 8 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: AAPM Bulletin 1214-1408, Publication (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Box: 19, Folder: 1 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: AAPM Bulletin 954-1213, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Box: 19, Folder: 2 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Detroit Wage Rate Report, Publication (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Box: 19, Folder: 3 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: AAPM Bulletin 1409-1518, Publication (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Box: 19, Folder: 4 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Replacement Parts Plants having a Normal Employment, Publication (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Box: 19, Folder: 5 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Legal Department Bulletins and Confidential Reports on Wages, Publication (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Box: 19, Folder: 6 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: What the Association Is and Does, Publication (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Box: 19, Folder: 7 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Radiator Group (Wage) Report, Publication (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Box: 19, Folder: 8 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Legislative Prohibition of Time Study, Publication (Box 19, Folder 8)
    By Clarence O. Skinner. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Small Group Reports, Publication (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Wage and Hour Statistical Data, Publication (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: AAPM Bulletins, Publication (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: Trade Survey, Publication (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Box: 20, Folder: 1 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Wage Rate Report from Various Plants, Publication (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Group Report from Various Areas, Publication (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Box: 20, Folder: 2 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Small Group Reports, Publication (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Wage and Hour Statistical Data, Publication (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: AAPM Bulletins, Publication (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Box: 20, Folder: 3 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Instrument Group Report, Publication (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Box: 20, Folder: 4 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Wheel and Rim Group Reports, Publication (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Box: 20, Folder: 5 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Universal Joint Group Report, Publication (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Universal Joint Group Wage Report, Publication (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Universal Joint Group Wage Report, Publication (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Universal Joint Group Wage Report, Publication (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Universal Joint Group Wage Report, Publication (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Universal Joint Group Wage Report, Publication (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: Universal Joint Group Wage Report, Publication (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: Universal Joint Group Wage Report, Publication (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Item 9: Universal Joint Group Wage Report, Publication (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Item 10: Universal Joint Group Wage Report, Publication (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Item 11: Universal Joint Group Wage Report, Publication (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Item 12: Universal Joint Group Wage Report, Publication (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Item 13: Universal Joint Group Wage Report, Publication (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Item 14: Universal Joint Group Wage Report, Publication (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Item 15: Universal Joint Group Wage Report, Publication (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Item 16: Universal Joint Group Wage Report, Publication (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Item 17: Universal Joint Group Wage Report, Publication (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Box: 20, Folder: 6 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Memo to Management re. inspiring workers, Publication (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Memo to Management re. American military power, Publication (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: AAPM Bulletin 1867(2)-1907(2), Publication (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Box: 20, Folder: 7 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: AAPM Bulleting 1810(2)-1856(2), Publication (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Wage and Hour Statistical Data, Publication (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Washington Bulletin, Publication (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Box: 20, Folder: 8 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Cleveland Wage Rate Report, Publication (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Box: 20, Folder: 9 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Piston Ring Group Report, Publication (Box 20, Folder 9)
- Box: 20, Folder: 10 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Michigan Rate Report, Publication (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Box: 20, Folder: 11 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Axle Group Report, Publication (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: Bumper Group Report, Publication (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Item 3: Carburetor Group Report, Publication (Box 20, Folder 11)
- Box: 21, Folder: 1 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Agreement between Bell and Hourly Rated Accounting Department Employees of Amalgamated Local 516, UAW-CIO and The International Union United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Publication (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Agreement between Bell and Fire Captain Union Local 516, UAW-CIO and The International Union United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Publication (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Agreement between Bell and Local Union 516, Inspection Union, UAW-CIO and The International Union United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Publication (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Agreement between Bell and Local Union 501, Inspection Union, UAW-CIO and The International Union United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Publication (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Agreement between Bell and Local Union 516, Timekeepers Unit, UAW-CIO and The International Union United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Publication (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Employment Forms, Publication (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Agreement between Bell and Local Union 516, Mold Loft Unit, UAW-CIO, The International Union United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Publication (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: Agreement between Bell and United Plant Guard Workers of America, Buffalo Local, Publication (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: Agreement between Bell and Local Union 516, UAW, Publication (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: Agreement between Bell and Local Union 516, Production Control Office and Materials Control Office Unit, UAW-CIO, Publication (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: Agreement between Bell and Time-Keepers Unit, UAW-CIO, Publication (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: Agreement between Bell and Production Engineering Technical Assoc., Publication (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Item 13: Agreement between Bell and International Union, UAW-CIO, Local 501, Publication (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Item 14: Group Insurance Plan, production and maintenance employees, Publication (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Item 15: Employees' group insurance benefits and contributions, Publication (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Item 16: Bell Aircraft News, Publication (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Item 17: Industrial Relations Policies and Procedures Manual, Publication (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Item 18: Training Course - Finishing, Publication (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Item 19: Training Course - Spot Welding, Publication (Box 21, Folder 1)